{
    "subject": "resource/Battle_of_Hattin",
    "predicate": "ontology/commander",
    "object": "resource/Al-Afdal_ibn_Salah_ad-Din",
    "human_readable": "The commander of the Battle of Hattin was Al-Afdal ibn Salah ad-Din.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.963310718536377,
            "question": "Al-Afdal ibn Salah ad-Din's role was as the commander during which battle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9451645016670227,
            "question": "What battle did Al-Afdal ibn Salah ad-Din command?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9149816036224365,
            "question": "What was the name of the commander who led in the Battle of Hattin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9137190580368042,
            "question": "Who commanded the Battle of Hattin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7361581921577454,
            "question": "Al-Afdal ibn Salah ad-Din is known for leading which significant battle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.667101263999939,
            "question": "Name the individual responsible for leading the forces in the Battle of Hattin."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6547850370407104,
            "question": "Which famous battle did Al-Afdal ibn Salah ad-Din oversee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6127103567123413,
            "question": "Identify the military leader associated with the Battle of Hattin."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5369595885276794,
            "question": "Who was in charge of the military operations at the Battle of Hattin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45315423607826233,
            "question": "In what historical event was Al-Afdal ibn Salah ad-Din a key figure?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The commander of the Battle of Hattin was Al-Afdal ibn Salah ad-Din.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2783_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was in charge of the military operations at the Battle of Hattin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2783_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Identify the military leader associated with the Battle of Hattin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2783_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which famous battle did Al-Afdal ibn Salah ad-Din oversee?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2783_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2783_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2783_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2783_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2783_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2783_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2783_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2783_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2783_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2783_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2783_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents state that Saladin was the commander of the forces at the Battle of Hattin.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}\n\nThe documents mention that Saladin (Salah ad-Din Yusuf) was the leader of the Ayyubid dynasty and a prominent Muslim military commander who led the forces in the Battle of Hattin. However, they do not indicate that Al-Afdal ibn Salah ad-Din was the commander of the battle. In fact, the documents mention Saladin as one of the commanders on the Ayyubid side, along with Gokbori, Al-Muzaffar Umar, and Al-Adil I, among others."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the documents provided, under the section detailing the battle and its participants, it is stated that one of the commanders for the Ayyubid forces was indeed Al-Afdal ibn Salah ad-Din. This supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Al-Afdal ibn Salah ad-Din was a son of Saladin, but he did not command the army at the Battle of Hattin. Instead, the commander of the Ayyubid forces in the battle was Saladin himself.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several provided text passages explicitly state that Saladin was the commander of the Ayyubid forces at the Battle of Hattin.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Al-Afdal ibn Salah ad-Din was the commander of Saladin, but not at the Battle of Hattin.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}